http://riversidehealthcare.ca/website-privacy-statement

Community Counselling
Diagnostic Imaging [X-Ray]
Search
Select LanguageEnglishAfrikaansAlbanianArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBulgarianCatalanCroatianCzechDanishDutchEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekHaitian CreoleHebrewHindiHungarianIcelandicIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseKoreanLatvianLithuanianMacedonianMalayMalteseNorwegianPersianPolishPortugueseRomanianRussianSerbianSlovakSlovenianSpanishSwahiliSwedishThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduVietnameseWelshYiddish
x
Contact Us
Concerns & Feedback
Site Map
You are hereHome
Website Privacy Statement
A culture of privacy and data protection is actively fostered at Riverside Health Care.
Riverside Health Care Facilities Inc. (RHC) is committed to protecting the privacy of all information that you choose to share with us in relation to this web site. Our Website Privacy Policy is intended to ensure that any confidential information that we collect, use or disclose in providing services and health care is managed according to the best and most current privacy practices, and complies with all relevant privacy legislation.
In particular:
Log files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track visitors' movements on the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
We use cookies to help improve the content within our site by helping us understand how visitors use and how many times the same visitor will revisit our site. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. This can be done through your browser. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookie acceptance. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features provided by various websites, including personalized login sessions and the storage of your personal preferences.
Sharing
We reserve the right to share aggregated demographic information with various departments throughout RHC. This information is not linked to any personal information that can identify an individual. For example, a department is notified that their portion of the website is the most visited section. As such, we would like to review and possibly expand the range of services provided within this portion of the website.
We occasionally partner with other parties to provide specific services. When a website visitor signs up for any services that are provided by such parties, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
Links and intermediaries
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that RHC is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our website visitors to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The statement you are reading now applies solely to information collected by this website. However, intermediaries such as internet service providers may make a record of your visit and log information to assist them in operating their businesses. In addition, in the unlikely event of an investigation, a law enforcement agency or other government agency may exercise its legal right to inspect logs of the hospital's internet service provider. Finally, this site does not provide facilities for secure transmission of information across the Internet. Users should be aware that there are significant privacy risks inherent in transmitting information across the Internet.
Notification of changes
If we decide to change this privacy statement, we will post notice of those changes on our website. If at any point RHC chooses to use personally identifiable information gathered on its website in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, users will be notified by email and have a choice if the hospital may use their information. Failing such notification, the hospital will use information in the manner described by the privacy statement in effect at the time the information was collected.
For information about the privacy of your personal health information, please visit our Privacy Home Page.
